export interface Blog {
  id: string;
  slug: string;
  title: string;
  excerpt: string;
  content: string;
  date: string;
  author: string;
  image: string;
  keywords: string[];
}

export const blogs: Blog[] = [
  {
    id: "1",
    slug: "mediumship-sacred-conversation",
    title: "Mediumship: A Sacred Conversation With Your Ancestors and Loved Ones",
    excerpt: "Mediumship is the bridge between this world and that one, a sacred conversation that allows healing words to finally be spoken...",
    content: `There is a moment in every mediumship session that I have never gotten used to, in the best way. It is the moment when a client's eyes well up, not from sadness, but from recognition. That is when I know the connection has come through.

I think of a man who once sat across from me, quiet and guarded, clearly unsure if any of this was even real. He had lost his father years earlier and had never really said goodbye. Within minutes of opening the connection, his father came through with a small detail, something so specific and so personal that there was no way I could have known it. A phrase he used to say. A particular habit at the dinner table. The man broke down, not in grief, but in relief. His father was not gone. He was simply on the other side of a very thin veil, still watching, still loving him.

This is the heart of mediumship. Our loved ones and ancestors do not disappear when they pass. Their energy continues, and with the right connection, that energy can still reach us, still comfort us, still guide us. Mediumship is the bridge between this world and that one, a sacred conversation that allows healing words to finally be spoken, questions to finally be answered, and love to keep flowing exactly the way it always did.

Many people come to me carrying unfinished business, words they wish they had said, forgiveness they wish they had asked for or given, or simply a longing to know their loved one is at peace. A mediumship session offers exactly that. It is not about predicting the future. It is about restoring connection, offering closure, and reminding you that love does not end where life does.

If you have ever wished for just one more conversation with someone you lost, or felt your ancestors quietly guiding you from behind the scenes, this is your invitation to listen more closely.

**Open the door to a conversation your heart has been waiting for.**`,
    date: "Sep 17, 2026",
    author: "Nattasha Sharma",
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1518531933037-91b2f5f229cc?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1200&q=80",
    keywords: ["mediumship reading", "talk to ancestors", "connect with loved ones who passed", "medium session", "Natasha Sharma"]
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    slug: "lama-fera-healing",
    title: "Lama Fera Healing: Ancient Himalayan Wisdom for Modern Healing",
    excerpt: "Lama Fera is an ancient Himalayan healing technique, practiced by Buddhist monks for centuries, that uses sacred symbols...",
    content: `**What is Lama Fera?** Lama Fera is an ancient Himalayan healing technique, practiced by Buddhist monks for centuries, that uses sacred symbols and mantras to channel divine healing energy. It is believed to clear negative energy, balance the seven chakras, and support healing on a physical, emotional, and spiritual level.

High in the monasteries of the Himalayas, centuries ago, Buddhist monks discovered something remarkable, a way to channel divine energy through sacred symbols and mantras to heal the body, mind, and spirit. That practice is called Lama Fera, and it is just as powerful today as it was then.

I think of a client who came to me carrying years of unexplained heaviness, not quite sadness, not quite illness, just a persistent sense of being weighed down. Traditional efforts hadn't shifted it. The moment we began a Lama Fera session, invoking those sacred symbols and channeling that ancient healing energy, she described it as feeling like something physically lifted off her shoulders. That heaviness she had carried for years finally had somewhere to go.

Lama Fera works by calling upon powerful, high vibrational healing energy and channeling it through sacred symbols, said to carry the blessings and healing power passed down through generations of Himalayan monks. This energy moves through the practitioner and into the person receiving healing, clearing negative energy, releasing karmic blockages, and restoring balance across the seven chakras.

What makes Lama Fera so powerful is its ability to work on multiple levels at once, easing physical tension, calming emotional turmoil, and awakening spiritual clarity, often within a single session. It doesn't just mask discomfort, it works to clear what's causing it at the root.

If you have been carrying a weight you can't quite explain, or feel like something in your energy has been stuck for far too long, Lama Fera may be exactly the ancient wisdom you need.

**Experience centuries of Himalayan healing wisdom for yourself.**`,
    date: "Sep 16, 2026",
    author: "Nattasha Sharma",
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1544928147-79a2dbc1f389?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1200&q=80",
    keywords: ["Lama Fera healing", "Himalayan healing technique", "chakra balancing", "energy healing", "Natasha Sharma"]
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    slug: "akashic-records-reading",
    title: "Akashic Records Reading and Healing: The Soul's Library Holds Every Answer You Seek",
    excerpt: "There is a place beyond time, beyond memory, where every choice you've ever made, every lifetime you've ever lived is recorded...",
    content: `There is a place beyond time, beyond memory, where every choice you've ever made, every lifetime you've ever lived, and every lesson your soul has ever learned is recorded. I call it the soul's library. Others know it as the Akashic Records. And every single time I open this space for a client, I am reminded that nothing about your journey has ever been random.

I remember a woman who came to me feeling completely lost. She had a good life on paper, a stable job, a loving family, yet something inside her felt unfinished, like she was living someone else's script. The moment I opened her Akashic Records, I understood why. Her soul had carried forward a pattern of playing small, of shrinking herself to keep peace, a pattern that stretched across more lifetimes than just this one. Once she saw it, once she truly understood where that pattern came from, something in her shifted. She wasn't broken. She was simply remembering.

This is what an Akashic reading truly offers. It is not fortune telling. It is remembering. Your soul already carries the answers to why certain patterns keep repeating, why certain relationships feel so familiar, why some fears seem bigger than this lifetime alone could explain. When we access the Akashic Records together, we are not guessing about your path, we are reading directly from the source, your soul's own record of truth.

And healing happens right there, in that same sacred space. Once a pattern is seen clearly, it can finally be released. Old vows, old fears, old agreements made in other lifetimes, all of it can be gently cleared, so you are no longer carrying weight that was never truly yours to carry in this life.

If you have ever felt like there is a bigger story behind your struggles, if you sense there is more to understand about who you are and why you are here, your Akashic Records are waiting to be read. This is not about predicting your future. It is about finally understanding your past, so you can walk forward lighter, clearer, and truly free.

**Discover the truth your soul has been waiting for you to remember.**`,
    date: "Sep 15, 2026",
    author: "Nattasha Sharma",
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1532012197267-da84d127e765?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1200&q=80",
    keywords: ["Akashic records reading", "Akashic healing", "soul records reading", "past life patterns", "Natasha Sharma"]
  }

,
  {
    id: "4",
    slug: "what-is-dragon-reiki",
    title: "What Is Dragon Reiki? A Gentle Guide to Attunement and Symbols",
    excerpt: "If you've spent any time exploring energy healing, you've probably come across Reiki. But lately, a deeper, more ancient-feeling branch has been quietly gaining a devoted following — Dragon Reiki...",
    content: `If you've spent any time exploring energy healing, you've probably come across Reiki. But lately, a deeper, more ancient-feeling branch has been quietly gaining a devoted following — Dragon Reiki. It sounds mythical, and in a way, it is. But it's also a real, practiced healing modality that thousands of people are turning to for something traditional Reiki alone doesn't always reach.

So what exactly is it, and why are dragons involved?

**Where Traditional Reiki Ends, Dragon Reiki Begins**
Classic Reiki works with universal life force energy — that gentle, steady current practitioners channel through their hands. Dragon Reiki takes that same foundation and adds something older and, many practitioners say, more potent: the energy of dragons.

In spiritual traditions across cultures — from Chinese and Japanese mythology to Celtic lore — dragons aren't seen as fearsome creatures to slay. They're guardians. Keepers of elemental wisdom, fierce protectors, and some of the oldest energetic beings believed to exist. Dragon Reiki practitioners work with these dragon guides to bring extra strength, protection, and depth into a healing session.

Where regular Reiki might smooth out everyday stress or tension, Dragon Reiki tends to be sought out for heavier lifting — old emotional wounds, karmic patterns that keep repeating, energetic boundaries that feel too thin, or a general sense of needing spiritual protection in your life.

**How Does Someone Actually Become a Dragon Reiki Practitioner?**
This is where attunement comes in, and it's really the heart of the whole practice. Attunement is a sacred, one-on-one initiation. A Reiki Master essentially opens up your energy channels so that dragon healing energy can flow through you safely and clearly. You can't pick this up from a YouTube video or a book — it has to be personally transmitted, almost like passing a torch.

Most Dragon Reiki training unfolds across three stages:
The **first level** is really about you. It opens your connection to dragon energy so you can begin healing yourself and offer simple hands-on sessions to others.

The **second level** is where things deepen. You learn distance healing — sending dragon energy to someone who isn't physically in the room — along with your first real symbol work.

The **third level**, the master level, is where a practitioner becomes fully equipped to hold space for complex healing work, and eventually to attune others themselves, continuing the lineage forward.

With each level, practitioners often describe feeling a noticeable shift — a raised sense of awareness, sharper intuition, and an easier, more natural flow when channeling energy.

**The Symbols That Bring Dragon Reiki to Life**
Every energy healing tradition has its symbols, and in Dragon Reiki, they're treated almost like keys — each one unlocking a slightly different kind of healing.

There's the **Dragon Fire symbol**, used when something needs to be burned away — old emotional baggage, stuck patterns, energy that's simply overstayed its welcome. Then there's the **Dragon Earth symbol**, which does the opposite job: grounding you, steadying the body, calming an aura that feels scattered or ungrounded.

When someone needs a shield rather than release, practitioners turn to the **Dragon Protection symbol** — often used for people who feel drained by others' energy or exposed to negativity. The **Dragon Wisdom symbol** is called on for clarity, for opening intuition when someone feels stuck or unsure. And the **Dragon Healing symbol** itself is the broad, all-purpose one — supporting physical recovery and emotional repair side by side.

These symbols are usually introduced during the second and third attunement levels, and practitioners use them through visualization, drawing them in the air, or simply holding the intention behind them during a session.

**Why People Are Drawn to It**
The people who find their way to Dragon Reiki often describe the same feeling — that traditional healing modalities helped, but something still felt unresolved underneath. Dragon Reiki tends to reach that layer. It's common to hear practitioners talk about clients releasing emotional patterns they'd carried for years, feeling their boundaries strengthen, or simply feeling more protected moving through daily life.

It also tends to resonate with people who are naturally energy-sensitive — the ones who absorb other people's moods easily, or who've always felt a pull toward something a little more ancient and mystical than mainstream wellness offers.

**Is Dragon Reiki Right for You?**
If you're someone who's tried energy work before and felt like you only scratched the surface, or if you're simply drawn to the symbolism of dragons as protectors and guides, Dragon Reiki might be worth exploring. It's not about intensity for its own sake — it's about depth, protection, and reconnecting with a form of healing energy that feels, to many practitioners, like it's been waiting to be rediscovered.`,
    date: "Sep 23, 2026",
    author: "Nattasha Sharma",
    image: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1601662528567-526cd06f363c?q=80&w=1200&auto=format&fit=crop",
    keywords: ["Dragon Reiki", "Dragon Reiki attunement", "Dragon Reiki symbols", "energy healing", "spiritual healing", "Reiki levels", "dragon energy healing"]
  }
];

